Guide to the Picture File, 1600s-1979 and undated, bulk 1814-1950
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Geographic Series, 1600s-1985 and undated, (10 boxes)
  - Japan, undated
    - "Japan Today - A Collection of Photographs by Germaine Kellerman - 1941," after 1941, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M180.4)
    - "Japan Today - A Collection of Photographs by Germaine Kellerman - 1941," after 1941, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M180.5)
    - "Japan Today - A Collection of Photographs by Germaine Kellerman - 1941," after 1941, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M180.6)
    - "Japan Today -- A Collection of Photographs by Germaine Kellerman -- 1941," 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M180.7)
    - "Japan Today - A Collection of Photographs by Germaine Kellerman - 1941," after 1941, (5 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M180.8)
      Includes exhibit cards.
    - Tokyo - old gold tower, undated, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M181)
      Emulsion flaking - handle with care.
  - Java, undated
    - Java market and transportation, undated, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Box 5, Folder M182)
  - Kentucky, 1800s, 1841 and undated
    - "Augusta College," 1800s, (lithograph) (Box 5, Folder M183)
    - "Coat of Arms of Kentucky," 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M184)
    - [Covington] "Western Baptist Theological Institute," 1841, (engraving) (Folder M185)
    - [Forest Retreat] "Gov. Metcalfe's Residence," 1800s, (lithograph) (Folder M186)
    - [Jonesville] "George Kean House," undated, (card photograph) (Folder M187)
    - [Lexington] "View of Insane Asylum," 1800s, (lithograph) (Folder M188)
    - "Main House at Shaker Village," 1800s, (lithograph) (Folder M189)
  - Korea, circa 1930s
    - "Glimpses of Chosen," circa 1930s, (2 viewbooks) (Box 5, Folder M190)
      "Chosen" is another word for "Korea."
  - Louisiana, 1800s and undated
    - "Louisiana - New Orleans," undated, (color lithograph) (Box 5, Folder M191)
    - [New Orleans] "Avenue of Live Oaks," 1800s, (2 stereographs)
    - [New Orleans] Custom House and French Market, 1800s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M192.1)
    - [New Orleans] "French Cemetery" and "Representation of the Exchange Hotel," 1800s, (2 clippings (Folder M192.2)
    - [New Orleans] Side vaults or ovens, Old St. Louis Cemetery, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M192.3)
    - Shreveport, undated, (stereograph)
  - Maryland, 1800s and undated
    - [Baltimore] B and O Railroad -- July 4, 1828, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Box 6, Folder M193)
      Photograph of a painting.
    - "Washington's Monument, Baltimore," 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M194)
  - Massachusetts, 1830-1906 and undated
    - "Boston in 1775," undated, (lithograph) (Box 6, Folder M195)
      From Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
    - "Boston - From the Harbour," undated, (lithograph) (Folder M196)
    - "Fanueil Hall, Boston," undated, (engraving) (Folder M197)
    - [Cambridge] "Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.," 1830 Sept. 1, (engraving) (Folder M198)
      From Geo. Hist. Society.
    - [Cambridge] "Hemenway Gymnasium - Harvard Summer School of Physical Training - 1906," 1906, (black-and-white photograph)
      From the Wilbur Wade Card Papers.
    - "Historical Massachusetts," undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M199.1)
    - "Historical Massachusetts," undated, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M199.2)
    - Longfellow's Home, undated, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M200)
    - [Salem] "'House of Seven Gables,' Residence of Nathaniel Hawthorne," undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M201)
  - Michigan, undated
    - [Dearborn] "The Edison Institute Museum and Greenfield Village," undated, (25 souvenir photographs) (Box 6, Folder M202)
      Includes case.
    - [Detroit] July 4 parade (?), undated, (card photograph) (Folder M203)
      Includes descriptive letter regarding the photograph.
  - Mississippi, 1800s-1963
    - [Biloxi] Life in Biloxi, 1900s, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Box 6, Folder M204)
    - [Mississippi River] "The Jolly Flatboatmen," 1800s, (black-and-white photograph of a painting) (Folder M205)
    - Natchez homes, 1900s, (7 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M206)
    - [Oxford] Courthouse, 1963 June, (color photograph) (Folder M207)
  - Missouri, 1927
    - Report on the St. Louis Tornado, 1927 Sept. 29, ( photograph album) (Box 6)
      Originally in album form; disbound and each sheet sleeved in original order. Original paper covers discarded.
  - New Jersey, undated
    - [West Long Branch] Shadow Lawn Mansion, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Box 6, Folder M209.1)
      From Monmouth College Photos.
    - [West Long Branch] Shadow Lawn Mansion, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M209.2)
    - [West Long Branch] Shadow Lawn Mansion, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M209.3)
    - [West Long Branch] Shadow Lawn Mansion, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M209.4)
    - [West Long Branch] Shadow Lawn Mansion, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M209.5)
    - [West Long Branch] Shadow Lawn Mansion, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M209.6)
    - [West Long Branch] Shadow Lawn Mansion, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M209.7)
  - New Mexico, 1942
    - "A Camera Report on El Cerrito - a Typical Spanish-American Community in New Mexico," 1942 Jan., Irving Rusinow, photographer, (album) (Box 6, Folder M210)
      This album contains about 75 black-and-white prints with descriptions.
      Published by U.S. Department of Agriculture.
  - New York, 1894-1901, 1800s and undated
    - Buffalo, (6 negatives) (Box 6)
      Removed to Negatives Series.
    - "New York in 1768," undated, (engraving) (Folder M211)
    - [New York] American Tobacco Company Offices?, 1894 and 1896, (2 card photographs)
    - Niagara Falls, 1901 Oct. 16, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M212)
    - Saratoga Springs, N.Y., undated, (stereograph)
    - "West Point and the Highlands," 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M213)
  - North Carolina, 1855-1985, 1800s and undated
    - Apex, 1975 July, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Box 6, Folder M214)
    - Asheville, undated, (5 card photographs) (Folder M215.1)
    - Asheville, undated, (5 card photographs) (Folder M215.2)
    - Asheville, undated, (5 card photographs) (Folder M215.3)
    - Asheville, undated, (4 card photographs) (Folder M215.4)
    - [Bath, Brunswick, and Carthage views], (2 card photographs and 1 black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M216)
      - [Brunswick] "Ruins of St. Philip's Church," undated
      - [Carthage] "The Cornwallis Tree," undated
      - ["Teach's Kettle," Bath], circa 1898
    - [Bath] St. Thomas Episcopal Church, undated, (2 card photographs) (Folder M217)
    - [Candor] School in Montgomery County, circa 1900, (card photograph) (Box 7, Folder M218)
    - [Chapel Hill] University of North Carolina, undated, (12 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M219.1)
      Includes original paper case for photographs.
    - [Chapel Hill] University of North Carolina, undated, (7 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M219.2)
    - [Chapel Hill] Caldwell Hall, circa 1935, (7 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M219a)
    - [Charlotte] Democratic State Convention, 1908 June 29, (postcard) (Folder M220)
    - [Durham] Bennett Place, circa 1947 and undated, 2 postcards and 4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M221)
      All images are of Bennet Place, with the exception of one, a photograph of the bottle Gen. Sherman and Johnston drank while drafting terms for the surrender.
      Two ink drawings were removed to OV20 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - [Durham] Bennett Place, 1925 and undated, (2 ink drawings
      Removed to Oversize Subseries from M221.
    - [Durham] "Bennett Place" -- home of James Bennitt, circa 1895-1931, (4 black-and-white photographs, 2 card photographs and 1 postcard) (Folder M222.1)
    - [Durham] "Bennett Place" -- home of James Bennitt, 1905 and 1900s, (2 card photographs and 1 postcard) (Folder M222.2)
      Includes a proclamation by North Carolina Governor Thomas J. Jarvis, and a note from the original owner of some of these photographs.
    - [Durham -- Bennett Place scenes], undated, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M223)
    - [Durham -- Blacknell house moving], 1985 June, (12 color photographs) (Folder M224.1)
    - [Durham -- Blacknell house moving], 1985 June, (11 color photographs) (Folder M224.2)
    - [Durham] Blacknell, William Thomas -- Home, undated, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M225)
    - [Durham] Burch, George Washington -- Home, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M226)
    - [Durham] The Citizen's National Bank, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M227)
    - [Durham] Civic Center -- Surgeons' Dinner, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M228)
    - [Durham] Commonwealth Cotton Mfg. Co., undated, (card photograph) (Folder M229)
    - [Durham] Downtown, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M230)
    - [Durham] Duke, B.L. -- Leaf Tobacco Broker, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M231)
    - [Durham] "Fairview," Home of Washington Duke, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M232)
    - [Durham] First Graded School, 1883, (card photograph) (Folder M233)
      Given by Miss Carrie Burch of Durham, NC.
    - [Durham] First Presbyterian Church (the First Church) and Manse, undated, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M234)
      Gift of M.E. Boyd Hamilton.
    - [Durham] Graded School in East Durham, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M235)
    - Durham High School Class of 1956, 1956 May 4, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M236)
      Includes list of addresses of graduates as of 1956.
    - [Durham] Home of Brodie Leonidas Duke, 1883, (card photograph) (Folder M237)
    - [Durham] Home of Washington Duke, undated, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M238)
    - [Durham] North Carolina Mutual and Provident Association Buildings, 1900s, (1 black-and-white photograph and 2 card photographs) (Folder M239)
      One color engraving was removed to OV21 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - [Durham] North Carolina Mutual and Provident Association Buildings, 1900s, (color engraving)
      Removed to the Oversize Subseries from M239.
    - [Durham] Old Courthouse, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M240)
    - [Durham] Pearl Cotton Mills, 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M241)
    - [Durham] S.R. Carrington's Bar and other buildings..., 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M242)
    - [Durham] Street Scenes, circa 1900-1905, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M243.1)
    - [Durham] Street Scenes, circa 1900, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M243.2)
    - Durham Traction Co. Light and Power Plant, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M244)
    - [Durham] Trinity Methodist Church, dedicated April 27, 1887, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph)
    - [Durham] Various Views, 1900s, (2 card photographs and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M245)
    - [Durham] Water Works, 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M246)
      Photographs include descriptions on the back.
    - [Durham] Watts, George Washington -- Home, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M247.1)
    - [Durham] Watts, George Washington -- Home, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M247.2)
    - [Durham] Watts, George Washington -- Home, undated, (5 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M247.3)
    - [Durham] Watts Hospital, 1915, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M248)
    - [Durham] W. Duke, Sons and Co.'s Factory, 1883, (card photograph) (Folder M249)
    - [Durham] West Durham School Classes, undated, (2 card photographs) (Folder M250)
    - [Durham] Wright, Richard Harvey -- Home, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Box 8, Folder M251)
      Includes note identifying previous owner.
    - East Durham Concert Band, 1910 July 4, (postcard) (Folder M252)
      Includes note from the donator and another note identifying a member of the band.
    - [Fayetteville] "View Of Fayetteville," undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M253)
      Photograph of a lithograph.
    - [Greenville] East Carolina Training School for Teachers, undated, (postcard) (Folder M254)
    - [Halifax County] Prospect Hill, near Airlie, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M255.1)
    - [Halifax County] Prospect Hill, near Airlie, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M255.2)
    - [Kittrell] Normal and Industrial Institute, undated, (5 card photographs) (Folder M256)
    - Lakeview Mineral Spring, Moore County, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M257)
    - "Land of the Sky" series -- W.D. Sprague's Hotel at Henry's Station, undated, (stereograph)
    - [Lenoir] Art Studio of Amanda Clarke Blackwell, circa 1890s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M258)
    - [Lincolnton] Lincoln Hospital, undated, (negative)
    - [Manteo] Monument to the Lost Colony, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M259)
    - [New Bern] "The Tryon Palace," undated, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M260)
    - [North Carolina scenes], 1865 Mar. 11 -- 1936 Oct., (2 card photographs and 3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M261)
      - "Arsenal at Fayetteville," 1865 Mar. 11
        Photograph of a sketch. Negative available. "Historical Department N.C. Division U.D.C."
      - [Franklinville] Old free school Academy, 1904 Dec. 23
      - [Hickory] New M. E. Church South, undated
      - [High Point] Inn of Nathan Hunt, 1936 Oct.
      - [High Point] Springfield Museum of Old Domestic Life, 1936 Aug. 15
    - [Raleigh] Home of Marshall DeLancey Haywood, undated, (postcard) (Folder M262)
    - [Raleigh] Peace Institute, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M263)
    - [Randolph County] Free's School house, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M264)
    - [Randolph County] Hopewell Methodist Church, 1936 Oct., (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M265)
      "Not original church, but place where many... founders are buried."
    - [Roxboro] Brooksdale Methodist Church, undated, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M266)
    - Salem Female Academy, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M267)
    - [Salem] Moravian Buildings, Cemetery, etc., undated, (4 card photographs) (Folder M268.1)
    - [Salem] Moravian Buildings, Cemetery, etc., undated, (5 card photographs) (Folder M268.2)
      Three card photographs were removed to OV23 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - [Salem] Moravian Buildings, Cemetery, etc., undated, (3 card photographs)
      Removed to the Oversize Subseries from M268.2.
    - "The Smoky Mountains," 1873 Homer Martin and R. Hinshelwood, artists, (colored engraving) (Folder M269)
    - Swannanoa River, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M270)
    - [Trinity High School faculty and students], 1897, (card photograph) (Folder M271)
    - [Wake Forest] Johnson Medical Building, 1933, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M271a)
    - Waynesville, undated, Meriwether and Williams, photographers, (card photograph) (Folder M272)
    - [Waynesville] Methodist Church and Public School, circa 1890s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M273)
    - [Waynesville views and scenes], undated, (4 card photographs) (Folder M274)
    - [Waynesville views and scenes], late 1800s, (5 large-format black and white photographs, one mounted)
      Scenes of groups in front of public buildings, one close-up picture of ox-cart with oxen. Removed to Oversize Subseries, Folder 177, Box LG04.
    - [Wilmington] "First House Built in Wilmington, NC.," 1855, (engraving)
    - [Wilmington] First Sewer Line Being Laid, undated, (card photograph) (Box 9, Folder M275)
    - [Wilmington] "The Old Cornelius Harnett Residence...," 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M276)
  - Ohio, 1839
    - [Ohio engravings], 1839, (2 engravings) (Box 9, Folder M277)
      - "Episcopal Log-Church (in the woods) near Gambier"
      - "Log House in Ohio"
  - Palestine, 1899-1904
    - [Biblical locations and views], 1899-1900, (4 stereographs) (Box 9)
    - [Biblical locations and views], 1900-1901, (4 stereographs)
    - Jordan and the "Promised Land," West of the Cliffs of Moab, 1904, (stereograph)
  - Pennsylvania, 1700s-circa 1890, 1800s and undated
    - [Gettysburg reunion], circa 1890, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Box 9, Folder M278)
    - [Gettysburg views], undated, (12 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M279.1)
    - [Gettysburg views], undated, (13 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M279.2)
    - "Philadelphia," 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M280)
    - [Philadelphia] "The East Prospect of the City of Philadelphia in the Province of Pennsylvania," 1700s, (engraving) (Folder M281)
      Photocopy. Original in OV25 in the Oversize Subseries.
      From "Sketches of the Life and Correspondence of Gen. N. Greene."
    - [Philadelphia] "The East Prospect of the City of Philadelphia in the Province of Pennsylvania," 1700s, (engraving)
      This is the original removed from M281 to the Oversize Subseries.
    - [Philadelphia] University of Pennsylvania, 1765, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M282)
  - Peru, circa 1900
    - [Lifestyles of Peru], circa 1900, (8 black-and-white photographs) (Box 9, Folder M283.1)
    - [Lifestyles of Peru], circa 1900, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M283.2)
  - Philippine Islands, circa 1890s-1900s and undated
    - [Masbate] Officials at Masbate, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Box 9, Folder M284)
    - [Cagayan Province] Album de la Cagayan Province, 1900s, (4 card photographs) (Folder M285.1)
      The album is comprised of 17 photographs.
    - [Cagayan Province] Album de la Cagayan Province, 1900s, (4 card photographs) (Folder M285.2)
    - [Cagayan Province] Album de la Cagayan Province, 1900s, (4 card photographs) (Folder M285.3)
    - [Cagayan Province] Album de la Cagayan Province, 1900s, (4 card photographs) (Folder M285.4)
    - [Cagayan Province] Album de la Cagayan Province, 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M285.5)
    - [Manila and other subjects], circa 1890s, (8 color paintings (Folder M286.1)
    - [Manila and other subjects], circa 1890s, (8 color paintings (Folder M286.2)
    - [Manila and other subjects], circa 1890s, (8 color paintings (Folder M286.3)
    - [Manila and other subjects], circa 1890s, (4 color paintings (Folder M286.4)
  - Poland, undated
    - Karkow, Lezajsk, Stalowa Wola, and countryside, undated, (5 postcards (Box 9, Folder M287)
  - Scotland, undated
    - "Abbotsford," undated, (engraving) (Box 9, Folder M288)
    - Edinburgh Castle, undated, (6 engravings) (Folder M289)
  - Siam, undated
    - Ayuthia, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Box 9, Folder M290)
  - South Carolina, 1863-1963, 1800s, 1900s and undated
    - Beaufort, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Box 9, Folder M291.1)
      These photographs were compiled for "Tales of Beaufort" by Nell S. Graydon -- Beaufort Bookshop, Inc. Beaufort, S.C., 1963.
    - Beaufort, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M291.2)
    - Beaufort, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M291.3)
    - Beaufort, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M291.4)
    - Beaufort, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M291.5)
    - Beaufort, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M291.6)
    - Beaufort, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M291.7)
    - Beaufort, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M291.8)
    - Beaufort, undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M291.9)
    - Beaufort, undated, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M291.10)
    - [Charleston] "Appearance of Fort Sumter on Sunday Afternoon -- August 23d 1863...," undated, (lithograph)
      Removed to OV Folder 2, Box SM01, Oversize Subseries.
    - [Charleston] "Charleston, S.C. and Its Vicinity," 1863, (engraving) (Box 10, Folder M292)
    - [Charleston] Earthquake Scenes, 1886 Sept., (7 card photographs) (Folder M293.1)
    - [Charleston] Earthquake Scenes, 1886 Sept., (7 card photographs) (Folder M293.2)
    - [Charleston] Earthquake Scenes, 1886 Sept., (6 card photographs) (Folder M293.3)
    - [Charleston] Earthquake Scenes, 1886 Sept., (6 card photographs) (Folder M293.4)
    - [Charleston] Earthquake Scenes, 1886 Sept., (2 card photographs) (Folder M293.5)
    - [Charleston] "East Battery," undated, W. Courtenay Corcoran, artist, ( sketch (Folder M294)
      Photocopy of original.
    - [Charleston] The French Protestant Church, 1888, (lithograph)
      Removed to Folder OV27, Box LG02, Oversize Subseries.
    - [Charleston scenes], undated, (5 stereographs)
    - [Charleston scenes], undated, (4 stereographs)
    - [Charleston -- stereograph of Magnolia Cemetery], undated, (stereograph)
      Removed to Stereographs Series
    - [Charleston] "Sunset View of Fort Sumter Before the Bombardment," undated, (engraving) (Folder M295)
    - [Charleston Views], 1900s, (14 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M296)
    - [Charleston] "Views of Charleston, the Capital of South Carolina," undated, (3 paper prints)
      Removed to Folder OV28, Box LG02, Oversize Subseries.
    - [Charleston] Wharf, Ruins of Circular Church and Judge King Mansion, 1800s, (3 card photographs) (Folder M297)
    - [Charleston] William Washington Home, South Battery, undated, (postcard) (Folder M298)
    - "Fort Sumter 1860," undated, W. Courtenay Corcoran, artist, ( sketch (Folder M299)
    - "To His Excellency James Glen Esq.," 1700s, (engraving)
      Removed to Folder OV29, Box LG02, Oversize Subseries.
    - Main Building -- Erskine College, Due West, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M300)
    - [Morris Island] "Attack on Fort Wagner," undated, Thomas Nast painter, (lithograph) (Folder M301)
      One stereograph removed to S27 in the Stereographs Series.
    - [Morris Island] Sea Front of Fort Wagner, circa 1865, (stereograph)
      Removed from M301 to the Stereograph Series.
    - [Orangeburg] Claflin University, circa 1888, (4 card photographs) (Folder M302.1)
    - [Orangeburg] Claflin University, circa 1888, (4 card photographs) (Folder M302.2)
    - [Orangeburg] Claflin University, circa 1888, (5 card photographs) (Folder M302.3)
    - [South Carolina buildings], undated, (7 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M303)
    - [Spartanburg -- Wofford college students], undated, (card photograph) (Folder M304)
    - "St. Phillip's Church, Charleston, S.C.," 1897, (engraving)
      Removed to Folder OV30, Box LG02, Oversize Subseries.
    - [Stereograph of Charleston], 1800s, (stereograph)
  - Sweden, 1700s
    - "Koniglicherpallast in Stockholm," 1700s, (engraving) (Box 10, Folder M305)
  - Tennessee, 1864 and undated
    - Chattanooga, Lookout Mountain and Battlefield, undated, (album, souvenir) (Box 10, Folder M306)
    - Coat of Arms of Tennessee, undated, (engraving) (Folder M307)
    - "The Falls of Fall Creek Near Smithville, Tenn.," undated, (lithograph) (Folder M308)
    - [Franklin] Carter House Gin and Screw. Morning after battle Nov. 30, 1864, 1864 Nov. 30, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M309)
      Photograph of an original pencil sketch.
    - [Memphis river steamer], undated, (card photograph) (Folder M310)
    - Mocassin Bend and Lookout Battlefield, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M311)
    - [Nashville] The Hermitage, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M312)
    - [Nashville -- views of the hermitage], undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M313.1)
    - [Nashville -- views of the hermitage], undated, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M313.2)